<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on Francis Laguna-Driscoll - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://frankld.netlify.com/categories/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on Francis Laguna-Driscoll - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 04:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://frankld.netlify.com/categories/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearts and Homes for Refugees</title>
      <link>https://frankld.netlify.com/post/hearts-and-homes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frankld.netlify.com/post/hearts-and-homes/</guid>
      <description>HHR is a non-profit humanitarian group focused on supporting government-approved agencies that welcome, protect and advocate for refugees in their new communities. They brought me on board to create a more seamless web experience for the end-user and to showcase the positive work that they are doing for this ongoing crisis.
Tasks The project is being built on mezzanine a content management system based on the Django web framework. We hope to introduce reusable components that will be spread across the entirety of the website with the goal of educating people on the proper definitions being used in the refugee crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GAMLP Social Media Illustrations</title>
      <link>https://frankld.netlify.com/post/gamlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frankld.netlify.com/post/gamlp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction 
Government Work Social Media Post offering recommendations on how to conserve water. Created for the Mayor’s Office in La Paz Bolivia
Vector Art Using Illustrator In this tutorial, commands that you enter will start with the &amp;ldquo;$&amp;rdquo; prompt. The output will follow. Lines that start with &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; are comments that I&amp;rsquo;ve added to explain a point. When I show updates to a file, the &amp;ldquo;:wq&amp;rdquo; on the last line means to save the file.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>